A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation photographs FA003
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation photographs
circa 1905-1980
FA003
Rockefeller Archive Center
1.0 cubic ft. Actual extent is unknown.
Rockefeller Foundation.; Photographs
- Unidentified Photographs
  - International Development Advisory Board - Report
- Rockefeller Foundation - International
  - Untitled (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    Statuary, art.
  - Animals (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Animals, experiments, field stations, monkeys, cows, Rio de Janeiro.
  - Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Meetings, conferences, speeches, group portraits.
  - Atomic Energy (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Meetings, group portraits.
  - B (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Blood bank, bequests, landscapes, medical laboratories.
  - Child Care Conference (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Group portraits, conferences, meetings.
  - Clarke Publications (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Cross-reference sheet only.
  - Congress for Cultural Freedom 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Dance, performing arts.
  - Congress for Cultural Freedom (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Congress for Cultural Freedom - Hungarian Performing Artists (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - D (Box 1, Folder 11)
    DNA research, parasites.
  - Diplomatic Service (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Buildings, cityscapes.
  - Economic Commission to Europe (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Education, scholarship recipients.
  - Fish (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Fish, animals, Brazil, Philippines.
  - G (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Geneva, research centers.
  - I (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Plaques, awards.
  - Incinerators (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Waste disposal, incinerators.
  - International Congress on Tropical Medicine and Malaria (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Group portraits, meetings, conferences.
  - International Council of Nurses Congress (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Nurses, group portraits, meetings, conferences.
  - International Health Division - Laboratories (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Laboratories, equipment, experiments, bacteria.
  - International Health Division - Laboratories - Rockefeller Institute (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Laboratories, field stations, graphs.
  - International Health Division - Laboratories - Vaccine Manufacturing (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Vaccinations, inoculations, yellow fever, typhus, administration, group portraits, medical staff.
  - International Press Institute (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Buildings, exteriors, interiors.
  - Laboratories (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Laboratories, experiments, scientific research.
  - Latrines (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Latrines, privies.
  - League of Nations (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Group portraits, Java.
  - League of Nations - Economic and Financial Sections - Intitute for Advanced Study (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Group portraits, candids.
  - Microphotography (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Equipment, photographic.
  - Mosquitoes 1 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Mosquitos, insects, identification of.
  - Penicillin (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Penicillin, medication.
  - Photography (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Photomontage (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Photography, RF, programs.
  - Photomontage (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Portraits (A) (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Patient, Africa.
  - Portraits - Acosta G., Dr. and Mrs. Alfonso (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Group portraits.
  - Portraits - Agar, John G. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Portraits - Aitken, Thomas H. G. (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Awards.
  - Portraits - Albani, Felix (FAO) (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Portraits - Albert I, King of the Belgians (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Portraits - Allen, Le Roy R. (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Portraits, candids.
  - Portraits - Anderson, Dr. and Mrs. Charles R. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Portraits - Anderson, Richmond K. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Portraits - Andrews, Chase (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Portraits - Arioiskandar, Raden Toemengoeng (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Portraits - Arnold, Virginia (Box 2, Folder 45)
    Portraits, group portraits.
  - Portraits (B) (Box 2, Folder 46)
    Cross-reference sheets only.
  - Portraits - Bailey, Charles A. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Portraits - Baird, Guy B. (Box 2, Folder 48)
    Informals, portraits.
  - Portraits - Baldwin, William H., Jr. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Portraits - Balfour, Marshall, C. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Portraits - Barber, Marshall A. (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Portraits - Barlow, Claude H. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Informal.
  - Portraits - Barnard, Chester I. (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Portraits - Barnes, Allan C. (Box 2, Folder 54)
    Portraits, RF Vice Presidents.
  - Portraits - Barnett, Doak (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Portraits - Bauer, J. H. (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Portraits - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Portraits - Beard, Mary (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Portraits - Becker, Eugene Jeno (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Portraits - Bell, F. W. (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Portraits - Bernard, Zdenek (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Portraits - Best, Charles H. (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Portraits - Bevier, George (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Portraits - Bigelow, Karl (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Portraits - Biggs, Herman M. (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Portraits - Bingham, Barry (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Portraits - Bishop, Eugene L. (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Portraits - Black, Davidson (Box 3, Folder 68)
    Peking Man, laboratories, candids.
  - Portraits - Bodian, David (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Portraits - Borbri, Vladimir (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Portraits - Borlaug, Norman E. (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Portraits - Borno, J. L. (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Portraits - Bourne, Leonard F. (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Portraits - Boyd, Mark F. (Box 3, Folder 74)
    Group Portraits, field work, portraits.
  - Portraits - Brace, Lloyd D. (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Portraits - Bradfield, Richard (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Portraits - Bronk, Detlev (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Portraits - Brumpt, Emil (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Portraits - Buchanan, Norman S. (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Portraits - Bugher, John C. (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Portraits - Bunche, Ralph (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Portraits - Burden, Robert P. (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Portraits - Buttrick, Wallace (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Portraits (C) (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Portraits - Calenberg, Constance (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Portraits - Calkins, Robert D. (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Portraits - Camargo, Luis Patino (Box 4, Folder 87)
    Portraits, laboratories, animal testing.
  - Portraits - Carr, Henry P. (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Portraits - Carter, Henry Rose (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Portraits - Castro, Aloysio (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Portraits - Causey, Calista E. (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Portraits - Causey, Ottis R. (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Portraits - Chagas, Carlos Pinheiro (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Portraits - Chandler, Robert F. (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Portraits - Chang, C. W. (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Portraits - Chao, W. J. (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Portraits - Chesley, Albert J. (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Portraits - Chuian, S. Hsipo (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Portraits - Clark, James Arthur (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Portraits - Cobb, William (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Portraits - Coggeshall, Lowell T. (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Portraits - Cole, Charles W. (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Portraits - Cole, Rufus (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Portraits - Coleman, James S. (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Portraits - Colwell, H. S. (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Portraits - Compton, Boyd (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Portraits - Connor, Michael E. (Box 5, Folder 107)
    Portraits, caricatures.
  - Portraits - Covington, Platt Walker (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Portraits - Crawford, Porter J. (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Portraits - Crawford, Robert W. (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Portraits - Crowell, F. Elisabeth (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Portraits - Cross, Howard B. (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Portraits - Crowder, Loy V. (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Portraits - Cummings, Mrs. Ralph (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Portraits - Curtis, General Newton Martin (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Portraits (D) (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Portraits - Dana, Doris (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Portraits - Darling, Samuel Taylor (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Portraits - Devinney, Leland C. (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Portraits - D'Arms, Edward F. (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Portraits - Davis, Jackson (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Portraits - Davis, Katherine Bement (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Portraits - Davis, Nelson C. (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Portraits - Day, Edmund E. (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Portraits - Dillard, James H. (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Portraits - Dillon, Douglas (Box 5, Folder 126)
    Group Portraits, J. George Harrar, John H. Knowles.
  - Portraits - Dinning, James S. (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Portraits - Docherty, John F. (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Portraits - Dochez, Alphonse R. (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Portraits - Doornick, John (Box 5, Folder 130)
    Portraits, laboratories.
  - Portraits - Downs, Wilbur G. (Box 5, Folder 131)
    Empty folder.
  - Portraits - Drensky, Kosta (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Portraits - Dublin, Louis I. (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Portraits - Dulles, John Foster (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Portraits - Dunlap, Dr. (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Portraits - Durck, H. (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Portraits (E) (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Portraits - Earle, Walter C. (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Portraits - Eastman, Dr. (Box 5, Folder 139)
    Initials are either J. W. or F. W.
  - Portraits - Ebert, Robert Higgins (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Portraits - Edsall, David L. (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Portraits - Eliot, Charles W. (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Portraits - Ellison, Ralph (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Portraits - Elmendorf, John B. (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Portraits - Embree, Edwin R. (Box 6, Folder 145)
    Portraits, Japan, China, Australia, Poland, group portraits, travel.
  - Portraits - Epstein, Miss (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Portraits - Estevez, Carlos (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Portraits - Evans, Roger F. (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Portraits (F) (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Portraits - Fahs, Charles (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Portraits - Favrot, Leo M. (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Portraits - Ferrell, John A. (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - Portraits - Fitzgerald, Alice (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Portraits - Fitzgerald, John G. (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Portraits - Flexner, Abraham (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Portraits - Flexner, Simon (Box 6, Folder 156)
    Laboratory scene, portraits.
  - Portraits - Fosdick, Raymond B. (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Portraits - Forsythe, W. A. (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Portraits - Freeman, Ruth B. (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - Portraits - Frenette, E. (Box 6, Folder 160)
  - Portraits - Freund, Gerald (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Portraits - Frissell, Hollis B. (Box 6, Folder 162)
  - Portraits - Frost, Wade Hampton (Box 6, Folder 163)
  - Portraits - Fujinami, Akira (Box 6, Folder 164)
  - Portraits (G) (Box 6, Folder 0164A)
  - Portraits - Gant, H. A. (Box 6, Folder 165)
  - Portraits - Germain, S. E. (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - Portraits - Gates, Frederick T. (Box 6, Folder 167)
    Portraits, Gates family, group portraits.
  - Portraits - Gibler, John W. (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - Portraits - Gilman, Daniel C. (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - Portraits - Gilmore, Raymond M. (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - Portraits - Gilpatric, Chadbourne (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Portraits - Gimaschewa, S. T. and Family (Box 6, Folder 172)
    Group portraits, Gimaschewa family.
  - Portraits - Gipson, Lawrence (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - Portraits - Goodpasture, Ernest W. (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - Portraits - Gorgas, William C. (Box 7, Folder 175)
    Portraits, military.
  - Portraits - Grant, John B. (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Portraits - Grant, Ulysses J. (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - Portraits - Grassi, Battista (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Portraits - Greene, Jerome D. (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Portraits - Greene, Roger S. (Box 7, Folder 180)
  - Portraits - Greenfeldt, John H. (Box 7, Folder 181)
  - Portraits - Gregg, Alan (Box 7, Folder 182)
    Portraits, homes, recreation, funeral monuments.
  - Portraits - Gregg, Lucien (Box 7, Folder 183)
  - Portraits - Greves, John H. (Box 7, Folder 184)
  - Portraits - Gunn, Selskar Michael (Box 7, Folder 185)
  - Portraits (H) (Box 7, Folder 186)
  - Portraits - Hackett, Lewis W. (Box 7, Folder 187)
    Portraits, laboratories, group portraits.
  - Portraits - Halverson, Wilton L. (Box 7, Folder 188)
  - Portraits - Hanna, Hugh (Box 7, Folder 189)
  - Portraits - Hanson, Haldore (Box 7, Folder 190)
  - Portraits - Hardin, Charles M. (Box 7, Folder 191)
  - Portraits - Harper, William Rainey (Box 7, Folder 192)
  - Portraits - Harrar, J. George - 1940's and Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 193)
  - Portraits - Harrar, J. George - 1950's (Box 7, Folder 194)
    Portraits, conferences, speeches, field stations.
  - Portraits - Harrar, J. George - 1960's (Box 7, Folder 195)
    Group portraits, Mexico, conferences, speeches.
  - Portraits - Harrar, J. George - 1960's (Box 8, Folder 196)
    Speeches, graduations.
  - Portraits - Harrar, J. George - 1970's (Box 8, Folder 197)
    Group portraits, India, field stations, dignitaries, graduations, speeches.
  - Portraits - Harrar, J. George - Retirement Dinner (Box 8, Folder 198)
    Celebrations, group portraits, dinners, parties.
  - Portraits - Harrison, John P. (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Portraits - Hata, Sahachiro (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Portraits - Havighurst, Robert J. (Box 8, Folder 201)
  - Portraits - Hayes, Guy S. (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - Portraits - Hayne, Theodore B. (Box 8, Folder 203)
  - Portraits - Heck, William H. (Box 8, Folder 204)
  - Portraits - Heger, Paul (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - Portraits - Heins, William A. (Box 8, Folder 206)
    Group portrait.
  - Portraits - Heiser, Victor C. (Box 8, Folder 207)
  - Portraits - Hepburn, A. Barton (Box 8, Folder 208)
  - Portraits - Hesburgh, Theodore M. (Box 8, Folder 209)
    Meetings.
  - Portraits - Hicks, Clarence J. (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Portraits - Hill, Rolla B. (Box 8, Folder 211)
  - Portraits - Hirzel, William (Box 8, Folder 212)
  - Portraits - Hopkins, Ernest Martin (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Portraits - Horsfall, Frank L. (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Portraits - House, Leland R. and Mrs. (Box 8, Folder 215)
  - Portraits - Howard, Hector Haldbrook (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Portraits - Hsu, Shih-ch'ang (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Portraits - Hudson, Paul (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - Portraits - Hughes, Charles Evans (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Portraits - Hulka, Jaroslav (Box 8, Folder 220)
  - Portraits - Hydrick, John L. (Box 8, Folder 221)
  - Portraits (I) (Box 8, Folder 222)
  - Portraits - Irwin, John N., II (Box 8, Folder 223)
  - Portraits (J) (Box 8, Folder 224)
    Cross-reference sheets and 2 copies of a photograph of Elmore Jackson.
  - Portraits - Jacocks, William P. (Box 8, Folder 225)
  - Portraits - James, Henry, Jr. (Box 8, Folder 226)
  - Portraits - James, Sydney Price (Box 8, Folder 227)
  - Portraits - Janney, John H. (Box 8, Folder 228)
    Children, medical exams, portraits.
  - Portraits - Jessup, Philip C. (Box 8, Folder 229)
  - Portraits - Johnson, Harald N. (Box 8, Folder 230)
  - Portraits - Jordan, Edwin O. (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Portraits - Judson, Harry Pratt (Box 8, Folder 232)
    Cross-reference sheet and 2 photocopies of images of Judson.
  - Portraits - July, Robert W. (Box 8, Folder 233)
  - Portraits (K) (Box 9, Folder 234)
  - Portraits - Kanter, Charles E. (Box 9, Folder 235)
  - Portraits - Kellogg, Vernon L. (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Portraits - Kendrick, John F. (Box 9, Folder 237)
  - Portraits - Kerr, J. Austin (Box 9, Folder 238)
  - Portraits - Kibler, W. H. (Box 9, Folder 239)
  - Portraits - Kimball, Lindsley F. (Box 9, Folder 240)
  - Portraits - Kimball, Richard T. (Box 9, Folder 241)
  - Portraits - King, A. F. A. (Box 9, Folder 242)
  - Portraits - King, Edith (Box 9, Folder 243)
    Archives, libraries, Rockefeller Archive Center.
  - Portraits - King, William Lyon Mackenzie (Box 9, Folder 244)
  - Portraits - Kingsley, Mary (Box 9, Folder 245)
  - Portraits - Kinnosuka, Miura (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - Portraits - Kirk, Robert Horner (Box 9, Folder 247)
  - Portraits - Kitasato, S. (Box 9, Folder 248)
  - Portraits - Kligler, Israel J. (Box 9, Folder 249)
  - Portraits - Kling, C. (Box 9, Folder 250)
  - Portraits - Klotz, Oskar (Box 9, Folder 251)
  - Portraits - Knapp, Seaman A. (Box 9, Folder 252)
  - Portraits - Knight, E. M. (Box 9, Folder 253)
  - Portraits - Knowles, John H. (Box 9, Folder 254)
    Group portraits, Rockefeller Foundation officers.
  - Portraits - Kumm, Henry A. (Box 9, Folder 255)
  - Portraits - Kuttler, Kenneth L. (Box 9, Folder 256)
    Laboratories.
  - Portraits (J) (Box 9, Folder 257)
  - Portraits - Labrecque, F. (Box 9, Folder 258)
  - Portraits - Lambert, Robert A. (Box 9, Folder 259)
  - Portraits - Lambert, Sylvester M. (Box 9, Folder 260)
  - Portraits - Langeron, M. (Box 9, Folder 261)
  - Portraits - Laveran, Charles L. A. (Box 9, Folder 262)
  - Portraits - Leach, Charles Nelson (Box 9, Folder 263)
  - Portraits - Leathers, Waller S. (Box 9, Folder 264)
  - Portraits - Leonard, Harold B. (Box 9, Folder 265)
  - Portraits - Lewis, Paul A. (Box 9, Folder 266)
  - Portraits - Ling, Hsuing Hai (Box 9, Folder 267)
  - Portraits - Link, Arthur S. (Box 9, Folder 268)
  - Portraits - Lloyd, Norman (Box 9, Folder 269)
  - Portraits - Lynaugh, Frances (Box 9, Folder 270)
  - Portraits - Lloyd, Wray D. M. (Box 9, Folder 271)
  - Portraits - Lyster, Theodore C. (Box 9, Folder 272)
  - Portraits (Mc) (Box 10, Folder 273)
  - Portraits - McClung, A. Colin (Box 10, Folder 274)
  - Portraits - McCune, Donald C. and Family (Box 10, Folder 275)
  - Portraits - McEvoy, Eileen (Box 10, Folder 276)
  - Portraits - McKelvey, John J., Jr. (Box 10, Folder 277)
  - Portraits - McKelway, Benjamin M. (Box 10, Folder 278)
  - Portraits (M) (Box 10, Folder 279)
  - Portraits - Machoux, Emile (Box 10, Folder 280)
  - Portraits - Mackintosh, James (Box 10, Folder 281)
  - Portraits - Macmillan, Eva (Box 10, Folder 282)
  - Portraits - Magoon, Estus P. (Box 10, Folder 283)
  - Portraits - Mahaffy, Alexander (Box 10, Folder 284)
  - Portraits - Mai, Li Ching (Box 10, Folder 285)
  - Portraits - Mann, Albert R. (Box 10, Folder 286)
  - Portraits - Manso, Caio (Box 10, Folder 287)
  - Portraits - Manson, Patrick (Box 10, Folder 289)
  - Portraits - Manuel, Leonard (Box 10, Folder 290)
  - Portraits - Marshall, John (Box 10, Folder 291)
  - Portraits - Masaryk, F. S. (Box 10, Folder 292)
  - Portraits - Mason, Max (Box 10, Folder 293)
  - Portraits - Maxcy, Kenneth F. (Box 10, Folder 294)
  - Portraits - Mei, Cheuk Shang (Box 10, Folder 295)
  - Portraits - Melnick, Joseph L. (Box 10, Folder 296)
  - Portraits - Mieldazis, Jerome J. (Box 10, Folder 297)
  - Portraits - Miller, F. A. (Box 10, Folder 298)
  - Portraits - Miller, Harry M., Jr. (Box 10, Folder 299)
  - Portraits - Mills, Ralph Garfield (Box 10, Folder 300)
  - Portraits - Milner, Ronald (Box 10, Folder 301)
  - Portraits - Missiroli, Alberto (Box 10, Folder 302)
  - Portraits - Mitchell, W. Leland (Box 10, Folder 303)
  - Portraits - Miura, Professor (Box 10, Folder 304)
  - Portraits - Miyairi, Keinosuke (Box 10, Folder 305)
  - Portraits - Moehiman, Raden (Box 10, Folder 306)
  - Portraits - Molloy, Daniel Murrah (Box 10, Folder 307)
  - Portraits - Morison, Robert S. (Box 10, Folder 308)
  - Portraits - Moseman, Albert H. (Box 10, Folder 309)
  - Portraits - Muhlens, Pedro (Box 10, Folder 310)
  - Portraits - Munro, N. Gordon (Box 10, Folder 311)
  - Portraits - Murdock, John (Box 10, Folder 312)
  - Portraits - Murphy, Starr Jocelyn (Box 10, Folder 313)
  - Portraits - Mustard, Harry S. (Box 10, Folder 314)
  - Portraits - Myers, Louis Guerineau (Box 10, Folder 315)
  - Portraits (N) (Box 11, Folder 316)
  - Portraits - Nagayo, Mataro (Box 11, Folder 317)
  - Portraits - New, Way Sung (Box 11, Folder 318)
  - Portraits - Nickel, John L. (Box 11, Folder 319)
  - Portraits - Niederhauser, John S. (Box 11, Folder 320)
  - Portraits - Nocht, Bernhard (Box 11, Folder 321)
  - Portraits - Noguchi, Hideyo (Box 11, Folder 322)
  - Portraits - Nolte, Richard E. (Box 11, Folder 323)
  - Portraits (O) (Box 11, Folder 324)
  - Portraits - O'Brien, Daniel P. (Box 11, Folder 325)
  - Portraits - O'Connor, Frank W. (Box 11, Folder 326)
  - Portraits - Ogden, Robert C. (Box 11, Folder 327)
  - Portraits - Oliver, Wade W. (Box 11, Folder 328)
  - Portraits - Olson, William C. (Box 11, Folder 329)
  - Portraits - Opie, Eugene L. (Box 11, Folder 330)
  - Portraits - Osler, Robert D. (Box 11, Folder 331)
  - Portraits - Oster, Katherine E. (Box 11, Folder 332)
  - Portraits - Owens, Patrick N. (Box 11, Folder 333)
  - Portraits (P) (Box 11, Folder 334)
    Cross-refference sheets only.
  - Portraits - Page, Walter Hines (Box 11, Folder 335)
  - Portraits - Pai, Hsui Lan (Box 11, Folder 336)
  - Portraits - Paine, Janet M. (Box 11, Folder 337)
  - Portraits - Pareja, W. (Box 11, Folder 338)
  - Portraits - Parker, Dorothy (Box 11, Folder 339)
  - Portraits - Parker, J. Cecil (Box 11, Folder 340)
  - Portraits - Parran, Thomas (Box 11, Folder 341)
  - Portraits - Pasteur, Louis (Box 11, Folder 342)
  - Portraits - Payne, George Calvin (Box 11, Folder 343)
  - Portraits - Paula Souza, Geraldo H. de (Box 11, Folder 344)
  - Portraits - Peabody, George Foster (Box 11, Folder 345)
  - Portraits - Pearce, Richard M. (Box 11, Folder 346)
  - Portraits - Pelc, Hynek (Box 11, Folder 347)
  - Portraits - Henrique A. (Box 11, Folder 348)
  - Portraits - Penna Chevarri, Dr. (Box 11, Folder 349)
  - Portraits - Perry, Jesse P., Jr. (Box 11, Folder 350)
  - Portraits - Peterson, Osler L. (Box 11, Folder 351)
  - Portraits - Pfeiffer, A. C. (Box 11, Folder 352)
  - Portraits - Ping-Wen, Kuo (Box 11, Folder 353)
  - Portraits - Pittaluga, Gustavo (Box 11, Folder 354)
  - Portraits - Po-Ling, Chang (Box 11, Folder 355)
  - Portraits - Proytchoff, G. (Box 11, Folder 356)
  - Portraits - Prudden, T. Mitchell (Box 11, Folder 357)
  - Portraits - Puech, L. R. (Box 11, Folder 358)
  - Portraits - Purks, J. Harris (Box 11, Folder 359)
  - Portraits (Q) (Box 12, Folder 360)
  - Portraits (R) (Box 12, Folder 361)
  - Portraits - Rachie, Kenneth O. (Box 12, Folder 362)
    Portraits, group portraits, Rachie family.
  - Portraits - Read, Florence M. (Box 12, Folder 363)
  - Portraits - Reed, Lowell J. (Box 12, Folder 364)
  - Portraits - Renfro, Bobby L. (Box 12, Folder 366)
  - Portraits - Rey, C. F. (Box 12, Folder 367)
  - Portraits - Rhind, Flora M. (Box 12, Folder 368)
  - Portraits - Richardson, Ralph W., Jr. (Box 12, Folder 369)
  - Portraits - Rickard, Elsmere R. (Box 12, Folder 370)
  - Portraits - Rivers, Thomas M. (Box 12, Folder 371)
  - Portraits - Roberts, Lewis H. (Box 12, Folder 372)
  - Portraits - Robinson, Edward (Box 12, Folder 373)
  - Portraits - Rockefeller, John Davison (Box 12, Folder 374)
    John Singer Sargent.
  - Portraits - Rockefeller, John Davison, Jr. (Box 12, Folder 375)
  - Portraits - Rockefeller, John Davison, 3rd (Box 12, Folder 376)
  - Portraits - Rockefeller, John Davidson (2) (Box 12, Folder 377)
  - Portraits - Rockefeller, Winthrop (Box 12, Folder 378)
  - Portraits - Romig, Robert and Mrs. (Box 12, Folder 379)
    Romig family
  - Portraits - Rose, Wickliffe (Box 12, Folder 380)
  - Portraits - Rose, Ronald (Box 12, Folder 381)
  - Portraits - Rose, Vernon (Box 12, Folder 382)
  - Portraits - Rowan, Walter Hawthorne (Box 12, Folder 383)
  - Portraits - Ruml, Beardsley (Box 12, Folder 384)
  - Portraits - Rupert, Joseph A. (Box 12, Folder 385)
  - Portraits - Rush, Benjamin (Box 12, Folder 386)
  - Portraits - Rusk, Dean (Box 13, Folder 387)
  - Portraits - Russell, Frederick F. (Box 13, Folder 388)
  - Portraits (S) (Box 13, Folder 389)
  - Portraits - Sabin, Albert (Box 13, Folder 390)
  - Portraits - Sawyer, Wilbur A. (Box 13, Folder 391)
  - Portraits - Saxton, Phillip (Box 13, Folder 392)
  - Portraits - Schapiro, Louis (Box 13, Folder 393)
  - Portraits - Schuffner, Wilhelm (Box 13, Folder 394)
  - Portraits - Schultz, Edwin W. (Box 13, Folder 395)